Those guys are monsters!
You really are a wonderful child, Chane.
I found him!
It's this guy, right?!
Bingo!
Hey!
うわあああぁ~~~っ !
ど どうしたの? 二一ス
Wh-What's wrong, Nice?
別に… 思い出し笑い
Nothing.
Just a reminiscent smile.
I see.
そう‥
Jacuzzi!
ジヤグジ一! あの爆薬は
知り合いの採掘場のおっちゃんと
We sold the explosives we received from an acquaintance at the mines...
...to a Hollywood movie technician on the black market!
ハリウッ ドの映画技師に
裏で買い取ってもらってよ!
合ゎせて ー0万 ドル
The grand total was $100,000.
ー0万 ドルだぜ ! すげえだろ !
$100,000, baby! Isn't that amazing?!
くジヤしざ~這》
あの手榴弾の陶器もよ
中身抜いたのカヾー個200ド丿し!
We also sold the empty hand grenades for $200 apiece.
そつかあ よかつた!
I see, that's great!
That aside, Jacuzzi...
それはそうとよ ジヤグジ一
ちよつと厄介なもん
拾つちまつてなあ
It seems we picked up something rather troublesome as well.
え? 何?
What?
いやな 箱につかまって
川に浮いてたんだよ
Well, there was someone clinging on to a box floating down the river.
乗客つつうか…
She was probably a passenger...
Big Sis, she's the one in the black dress.
疆さん 例の 黒いドレスの…
That woman?
あの女性ですか?
はい
Yes.
え 知り合いなの?
Is she an acquaintance?
I wouldn't exactly call her that.
知り合いつていう力
Well, if you say we know her,
then we do know her, but...
まあ… 知つてるつて言えば
知ってるんだけど…
In any case, we can't hand her over to the police, so we brought her here.
とにかく警察に渡すわけにもいかねえし
連れてきたんだよ
そうなんだ
それじゃ早く紹介してよ!
I see.
Hurry up and introduce her then.
Sure.
Come in!
入りな!
Hey! I'm Jacuzzi Splot.
やあ 僕はジヤグジ一スブロツ 卜!
歓迎するよ! 君の名前は?
Welcome! And your name is?
They said they won't give me permission to leave the hospital yet.
まだ退院許可は出せないつて…
I'm sorry.
ごめんね 何だか僕のせいで
付き添いみたいなこと させちやつて
Somehow, I'm to blame for making you attend to me like this.
ああ~! 僕に気を使わないで
読みたかつたら読んでよ
Don't mind me!
If you want to continue reading, please do.
あ 僕は新聞なんて
あんまり興味ないし
I'm not very interested in things like newspapers.
I'm not making fun of newspapers or anything!
あ 新聞なんてなんて 決して
バ力にしたわけじゃないんだよ
誤解しないでね
Please don't misunderstand me.
I just didn't want you to worry about me; that's all.
ただ 僕にあんまり気を使わないで
ほしいって それだけなんだ
Hey, Chane...
あのさ シヤ一ネ
シヤ一ネつて 名字が
ラフォレツ 卜だつたよね?
Your family name was Laforet, right?
Are you related to a man named Huey by any chance?
ひよつとして そのヒユ一イって人と
親戚か何かだったりするの?
ああ ああ… ごめんよ
I'm sorry!
If it's something you aren't comfortable talking about, then you don't have to.
もし込み入つた話なら
無理に話してくれなくてもいいし
And if you're unrelated to him and it's merely a coincidence, please forgive me.
もし関係なくて ただの偶然だったら
許してほしいし とにかくごめん!
Either way, I'm sorry!
それは私の父です
そ そうなんだ
"He is my father."
Is that so?
"I am one of the terrorists who attacked the train."
私は列車を蓑った
テロリス卜の伸間です
分かつてたよ
二一スや二ックの様子で何となく
I figured as much. I could tell from Nice and Nick's behavior.
なぜ通報しないのですか ?
"Why don't you turn me in?"
"Why?", you ask...
なぜつて そ り や あの列車で
Well, what those guys in black clothes did on the train is unforgivable,
黒服の人たちがやったことは
許せないけど
僕たちだつて 列車の貨物を
盗んだわけだから
but we stole the train's cargo as well.
大声で文句なんか言えないし…
We can't complain loudly either.
And besides, you seem like a good person for some reason...
それに 君は何となく
いい人そうだからさ
いや ほんとにいい人かどうかなんて
分からないけどさ
No! I don't know if you're really a good person or not.
But, it's fine. Because we're friends, right?
でもいいじゃない
友達なんだからさ
あなたたちは 私には
理解できない人たちです
"You guys are beyond my comprehension."
あなたたちつて
二一スやド二一のことかな?
"You guys"? I wonder if she means Nice and Donny.
That's how it is more or less.
大体そんな感じなんだけどね
信じられない?
Do you find it hard to believe?
それはそうだよね
そう簡単にはね
Well, I suppose it is.
Not that easily.
あんまり こういうの
見せたりしないんだけどね
I don't really show this quite often,
but you're special, Miss.
お姉ちやんは特別だよ
信じてくれた?
Do you believe me now?
あ はい
Yes.
I may be older than you, but...
僕のほうが年上だけど
気持ち悪いから
子供を扱うみたいに話していいよ
I find that disgusting, so it's okay to talk to me like I'm a child.
あ ありがとうございました…
Thank you very much.
No—
う いや ありがとう チ工ス君
Thank you, Czes.
お一一つ
ムチャクチヤ偶然だな オイ
What an unexpected coincidence!
I came to see my childhood friend, Firo.
俺は フイ一ロつて幼なじみに
会いに来たんだけどさ
It seems he went out with a couple he knows though...
あいつなんか知り合いの力ツプ丿しを連れて
遊ぴに行っちゃったらしくてさ
客が来てるのを
邪魔しちゃ悪いと思って
I thought it'd be rude to bother the guests, so...
I decided to go home today.
今日は帰ることにしたんだが…
お前らは何やってんだ?
いつの間に仲良くなったんだ?
What are you guys doing?
When did you two become friends?
Like I said, that woman, Chane, is nothing but trouble!
だから あのシヤ一ネつて女は
ヤバいっつったんだ
あんなの仲間にしといたら
絶対この先ヤバいですって
If we befriend such a person, we'd be in danger later on.
警察にも目ぇつけられるだろうし
We'd be under observation by the police too.
何しろテロリス卜の伸間だからネ一
She is one of the terrorists after all.
It's fine with me.
俺はいいけど
ジ工ノア一ドさんに
迷惑がかかるのはちょつと…
However, it may be of concern to Mr. Genoard.
でもジャグジ一が
決めたことなんですから
But, this is what Jacuzzi has decided, so...
姐さん…
Big Sis...
Indeed, she does seem rather suspicious, but...
確かに得体の知れない
女の子だけど
私たちと一緒で
...like ourselves, she has no one to depend on in these hard times.
身寄りがなくて
困っているのは事実なんだし
あ! シヤ一ネさん
Chane!
A-A package arrived for you earlier.
さ さつき シヤ一ネさん宛に
荷物が届いてましたよ
Wow!
すごい!
Isn't it lovely?
ステキじやないですか
着てみたらいかがですか?
シヤ一ネさん
Why don't you try it on, Chane?
お ? ああぁ
Excuse us.
これは失礼
ヒヤツハア
ステキ… よく似合つてますよ
It's beautiful. You look great!
誰が贈つてくれたんですか ?
Who sent it?
ピシヤ一ネ丿
あの男ヵら左…
どう乙 )う フも りなん左ろう ?
It's from that man.
What are his intentions?
{シヤ一ネ丿 旗…
A dress...
This is the first time someone besides my father has given me such a thing.
ピシヤ一ネ丿
こんな物きヱさん鱒又外の謹ヵ耀
槽られ庭のは初めごだ
Father used to make dresses for me when I was young.
父さんは 私ヵーさ〔 )頃な
よく互盧きこレらえ ごく力庭
ご ごも う力 レヵ フ庭
It made me happy.
But...
だソプど
あの男ノご涅皮きもらっご
How should I feel after receiving a dress from that man?
私はどうC )う感借に
な力ば乙 'こ 'のだろう
分ヵらな蝿 分ヵらな蝿
I don't know... I just don't know...
I simply don't understand him anymore.
あの男のこ ごヵ
ますま實分ヵらなくなっ庭
ぁの男は又さんき守ると言っ庭
その盧め仁 私と結婚するとも言っ庭
He said he would protect Father.
He also said he would marry me for that reason.
何き患 フ ご あの男が
ぁんなことき言っ盧の汝は分ヵらな‥
I still don't know why he said such things.
だヵ抄なく ご も あの男の言葉ノごな
ウ ソは感グらカな汝フ庭
But, at the very least...
I did not feel a lie in his words.
That's why I'm confused.
だ凌 ら私 は又崑劇 レ庭のだ
Even so, should I accept his proposal?
それならば私は あの男の牢レ出き
受ノプ入力るベきなのだろうか?
だヵ私は怖‥
私は何き恐ゎご蝿るの盧ろう?
But, I'm afraid...
What am I afraid of?
ぁの男は何き,雷っ ご こんな私 ノご
結鱈き牢レ込ん盧の盧ろう?
I wonder what that man was thinking when he chose to propose to me.
どうレご私にこんな物き…
Why did he give me something like this?
シヤ一ネさん どうかしました?
Chane?
Is something wrong?
そうですか…
I see.
シヤ一ネさん 気分転換に
出かけてみたら?
Chane, how about going out for a change?
あ グラハムさん
誰か出てきたっスよ
Graham, it looks like someone came out.
Is that so?
そうか 退屈な話にならないことを
祈るとしよう
Let's hope it doesn't turn out to be something boring.
ああ… 退屈は罪だ
Boredom is a sin.
人に与えられた限りある時間を
To not use life's limited time in idleness nor drowning in pleasure.
怠惰に過ごすでも
快楽に稟れるでもなく
An existence only to waste time.
ただ そこに存在するだけで
食いつぷしていく…
こんなこと耐えられない!
I can't bear it! Boredom is a sin!
退屈は罪だ ! 死ね ! 退屈は死ね !
Die, die boredom!
Die, die, die!
死ね 今 死ね
お前 死ね 俺 死ね
Wow, she's pretty cute!
うお~ すげえ かわいい子っスよ
退屈な時間というのは
Boring times are coffee breaks in facing the hardships of life.
人生の山場を完全な状態で
迎えるためのコ一ヒ一ブレイク
そう思うことにしよう
She makes you think that way. She's that cute, isn't she?
という格言が思いつくぐらいに
かわいい子じゃないか
She must be Eve Genoard after all...
あれがイブ ジ工 ノ ア一 ドですかね
やつぱり
If she's not, then she's not.
違つてたら違つてたで
I insist that it's the spice of life too.
それまた人生のスパイスだと
俺は主張したい
なぜなら この世界に退屈なことなど
何一つありはしないのだから
That's because there is no boredom at all in this world.
さつきと全然 違うこと言ってますが
大丈夫ですか? ボス
You're completely contradicting yourself now.
Are you okay, Boss?
You've become quite fearless after losing consciousness once, haven't you?
お前 ー回気絶してから
随分と怖いもの知らずになったな
They're entering Central Park.
セン 卜ラルパ一クに入り ますよ
I see.
そうか…
ならば悲しい話を紡き出すとしようか
Then, let's spin ourselves up a sad story...
For them, that is.
奴らにとつてのな
ヒヤツハア ?
ひゃっはあ
ヒャツハァ !
あん? 何だ?
What's that?
Let us begin the sad, sad story.
悲しい話を…
悲しい話を始めようじやないか
It'll be so sad your heart will break.
悲しみで胸が
張り裂けそうになる話だが…
Well, don't worry because I'll have fun.
まあ 俺は楽しいから安心してくれ
シヤグシ一!
Jacuzzi!
Wh-What's wrong, Nick and Nice?
ど どうしたの? 二ツク 二一ス
そんなに慌てて
You're panicking.
シヤ一ネさんが…
シヤ一ネさんが さらわれて
Chane was—
Chane was kidnapped!
_
ええ~~つ!? と とついつ」と?
H-How'd did it happen?
も もしかして警察に!?
C-Could it be the police?
そうじやねえんだ
It wasn't them.
こんなでつかいモンキ一レンチを
持つた奴が いきなり出てきてよ
Some guy with a monkey wrench this big suddenly showed up.
ぬおっ…
ひやつはあ
ぬあ…
親愛なるジヤグジ一スプロッ卜と
その一味の皆様へ
"Dear Jacuzzi Splot and the rest of the gang,
we have taken Eve Genoard hostage—
イブ ジ工 ノ ア一 ドは預かつた
助けたければ 出せるだけの金を持って
港のー3番地にある廃工場まで来い
If you wish to save her, bring all the money you have and come to the disposal plant at the port's 13th block.
むろんー 人でな
Alone, of course."
こ これ脅迫状だよ
し しかもイブつて…
This is blackmail!
M-Moreover, they said Eve...
It seems they've gotten their basics wrong.
何だか根本的なとこが
間違ってるよっ
このままじゃ
シヤ一ネヵヾ ひどい目に遭っちゃう!
At this rate, Chane will be in trouble.
ジヤグジ一
Jacuzzi!
Jacuzzi, are you seriously going?
ジヤグジ一 行くのかよ
わざゎざ あんなワケの分かんねえ
女のために
Especially for a woman you barely even know?
当たり前だよ
シヤ一ネは伸間だもの
Of course. Chane is our friend.
Jacuzzi! Even if you say that...
ジヤグジ一
伸間って言われてもよお
True, we may not know where she was born or how she was raised.
確かにシヤ一ネがどこで生まれて
どんなふうに育つたかなんて
分かんないよ
でもさ 二ツクみたいに
川を流れてきたんでしよ
However, she arrived here by floating down the river, didn't she?
That alone makes me feel like it's destiny.
何かそれだけで
もう運命みたいなものを感じるしさ
行く場所がなさそうなのも
僕たちと一緒だし
It seems she doesn't have anywhere to go either.
We're the same in that regard.
それに それにさ…
And... besides...
僕には どうしてもシヤ一ネが
悪い人には見えないんだ
No matter how I look at her, I don't think Chane is a bad person.
それだけなんだよ
That's all.
ジヤグジ一
Jacuzzi...
Nick, don't worry. I'll go alone.
二ック 安心して
僕ー 人で行くからさ
ジヤグジ一 それはダメ !
Jacuzzi! You can't!
Jacuzzi, that wrench wielding bastard isn't your average punk.
ジヤグジ一 あのレンチ野郎は
並の不良じゃねえぜ
それでも行くよ
行くしかないじゃないか!
Either way, I'm going.
There isn't any other way!
ー人で来いつて言うんだからさ
He said to come alone, that's why...
...it would be disrespectful if I didn't.
そうしなかつたら
相手にも失礼じゃない
こ 怖くて仕方ないけどさ…
I'm afraid and I can't do anything about that, but...
かわいそうに おぴえて声も
出せないみたいっスよ
It's sad, isn't it?
It seems she's so frightened she can't say a word.
My apologies, young lady.
悪いな お嬢ちやん
However, not being able to speak is joyous in its own regard.
だカヾ 声を出せないということは
ある意味 幸せなことだ
人は悲しみをロにするのも
喜ぴをロにするのにも
When people talk of sadness, of happiness, or of anger,
怒りをロにするのにも
非常に強い工ネルギ一を消費する
they use a substantial amount of energy in the process.
恐ーー布や苦痛となれば なおさらだ
Even more so when it's fear and suffering.
そういう意味では言葉を失うほどに
おぴえるというのは
In that sense, being speechless due to fear,
to some extent, conserves energy during extreme situations.
ある意味 極限状態において
工ネルギ一消費を抑えるための
杢間の本能が営む自衛行為だとは
言えないだろうか?
A self-defense mechanism brought about by human instinct...
...is it not?
ん~ しまつた
Damn.
匣は少々 頭のいいことを
言ってしまつたぞ
I've just said something quite clever.
よし ほめろ お前ら
All right! Praise me, you guys.
お一一
んん? おい
何勝手に立ち上力ヾつてる…
Hey! What are you standing up for—
Oh? I was under the impression you were just a rich lady, how interesting...
ほう ただのお嬢様かと思つたら
面白い物を…
Isn't that a little big for self-defense though?
そいつは護身用にしちゃ
ちょつと大きすきやしないか?
だ力ヾいい
But, it's fine...
I was a little surprised, but being surprised is a good thing.
少し蔦いたが
驚くのは いいことだ
Surprise is something which reminds humanity...
驚きというものは
常に人間に
人生は先の読めない闇だということを
思い出させてくれる
...that life is an unpredictable dark future.
Surprise number two...
驚き その2
You're not Eve Genoard, are you?
お前 ひよっとして
イブジ工ノア一ドじやないな
Your movements just now...
ちよつとこれ~
今の動きは素人じゃなかったかろな…
That isn't something a mere amateur could do.
その 正直 驚いたよ
I'm honestly surprised.
あと 人の話は最後まで
聞いてくれるとうれしい
Also, I'd be happy if you listened to everything I have to say.
ウツハハハハハハ
You're quite interesting.
面白いな お前
〇Kすきるほどに〇Kだ
You're just too good to be true.
Damn, I'm getting all fired up.
ヤバいな ヮクヮクしてきたよ
All right, I've decided.
よ し決めた
I won't be surprised even if you happen to be an alien from Mars.
もう俺はお前が
火星人だと言われても驚かない
さあ 早く
腕を 8本 生やしてみてくれよ
So, enough waiting. Let's see you grow eight arms.
人間じやないとなりや
壊しがいがあるっ乙もんだ
If you're not human, then it'll be worth tearing you apart.
フン !
ハツ !
Somehow, this has become quite enjoyable.
何だか愉快になってきたよ
実に実に愉快になってきた
Really, really enjoyable.
For the sake of spinning ourselves up a pleasant story, why don't we join forces?
愉快な話を紡き出すために
ここはひとつ 手を組もうじゃないか
To put it bluntly, surrender yourself.
具体的に言うと あれだ
俺に負けろ
やめて下さい!
Please stop it!
あの お金は
持つてきましたから
Um, I've brought the money, so...
だっ だから その子を
その子をすぐに放して下さい!
S-So...
Let go... Let go of that girl immediately!
そんなに大金つてわけには
いかないかもしれないけど
It might not be a lot of money, but...
I'm certain the amount will suffice.
それなりの金額にはなると思うから
S-So, with this money, please return that girl!
だから このお金で
その子を返して下さい!
ほほう 早かつたな
You're fast.
All right, then let's switch from a surprising story to my own happy story.
よし 驚きの話から
俺にとつての うれしい話に
物語をスイッチするとしよう
いやあ いい 金はいい
No, I don't care for money.
I don't understand why, but everyone says money is a good thing.
よく分からないが
みんないいものだと言う
フン そして その金に踊らされて
破減していく姿が
Also...
the way they're disillusioned by money and brought to ruin is absolutely marvelous!
最高にいい !
キヤツチ
Catch.
待てよ
金を持つてきたつて言うか
Wait...
You said you brought the money, but it's obvious you've come empty-handed.
どう見ても
手ぷらじゃあないのか?
手ぷらだけど
お金… つていうか
I may be empty-handed but, in actuality, I've brought something else instead of money.
代わりのものは
ちゃんと持つてきました
I-I don't know if you'll believe me or not, but...
し 信じてもらえるかどうか
分からないけど
僕Lま‥
I...
I have a bounty on my head from the Russo family mafia of Chicago!
僕はシ力ゴの丿しッソファミリ一っていう
マフィアに賞金をかけられてる
If you hand me over, you should be able to receive a generous reward.
僕の身柄を引き渡せば それで…
それなりの
お金を もらえるはずだよ
二一ス !
Nice!
はっ ジヤグジ一!
Jacuzzi?
Nice, open up! Nice!
二一ス 開けてよ! 二一ス!
Nice!
二一ス !
Open up, Nice!
開けてよ! 二一ス!
ジヤグジ一
Jacuzzi!
What's with that tattoo?
どうしたの? その刺青
いれずみ
See? With this, my face stands out now.
ほらね これで僕の顔は
見分けがつくよ!
So, if you're always by my side, it'll be all right!
だから ずつと僕が一緒にいれば
大丈夫だよ
Jacuzzi...
ジヤグジ一…
二一ス どうしたの?
Nice, what's wrong?
ごめん ごめんよ
I-I'm sorry!
そんなにぴつくりさせる気
なかつたんだよ
I didn't mean to surprise you that much.
あっ… 二一スが泣いてると
僕も泣きたくなっちゃうよ
If you keep crying, I'll start crying too...
僕はただ君の力になりたくて…
それだけで…
I just wanted to help you...
That's all...
そういう人なんですよ
シヤグジ一って
That's the kind of person Jacuzzi is.
自分のことより 人のことを考えて
行動しちゃうんです
He thinks and acts for the well-being of others rather than himself.
That's why we're always at a loss.
だから いつも損ばかり…
But, there are always many friends around him.
けど彼の周りには
いつも仲間がいつぱいいるの
お前 すごいな
You're really something!
Damn! You've touched my heart!
チクシ ヨ ウ 俺を感動させやがつて
How interesting! You're fun!
面白い お前 楽しいぞ
You're also sad, Jacuzzi Splot!
そして悲しいな
ジヤグジ一'スプロッ卜
However, I'm impressed!
だが感動だ !
楽しさと悲しさは
常に紙一重というが
It's said the line between pleasure and sadness is very thin!
お前は今 この瞬間 !
But, at this instant...
その紙の間に
俺の心を閉じ込めた
...you've shoved my heart in between the two.
However!
しかし !
At the same time, I'm having fun fighting this girl.
俺は同時に この女との戦いを
楽しんでいる!
ああ どうしよう!
What should I do?!
Should I release this girl as an act of respect for shoving my heart between pleasure and sadness?
俺の心を閉じ込めたお前に免じて
この女を解放するか
Or, should I disregard that and continue my fight with this girl?
それとも無視して
この女と戦い続けるか
俺の心は今 雪宣に乱れている !
My heart is in a state of disarray now!
あ壷 どうすればいい!
お別ならどうする!?
What should I do?!
What would you do?!
そ ヾ
れ力 答スか?
So that's your answer?
では 行くか
Then, let's get going.
Stop it! I'm begging you!
やめてよ お願いだから
殺し合いなんかやめて!
Stop this deathmatch!
うつ… あっ !
Chane, are you okay?
シヤ一ネさん 無事でしたか?
二一ス 開いているのに
なぜ爆発させる?
Nice, why did you blow up the door when it was already open?
んなこと
聞かなくても分かってんだろ?
You don't have to ask something so obvious.
姐さんは
ただ爆発させたかつただけだよ!
Big Sis just wanted to blow it up.
みんな‥
Everybody!
What's this? Didn't I write come alone in the letter?
あれ? 俺 手紙にー人で来いって
害いてなかったっけか?
Yes, just as the letter requested, Jacuzzi went alone.
ええ 手紙に害かれていたとおり
ジヤグジ一がー 人で行ったので
I came here alone as well.
私もー 人で ここまで来ました
ぬあ 俺ー人で来た
アメリ力まで メキシコから
Yeah, I came here alone from Mexico to America.
俺もー人で歩いて来た
I walked here alone, too.
俺も!
Me too, me too, me too! Me too...
It's true you're not contradicting the letter...
確かに矛盾はしていない…
さてはお前ら 頭がいいとみえる
You guys look smart.
Wh-What are we gonna do with these guys?
どつ どうするんですか こいつら!
みんな 来てくれてありがとう
Everybody, thanks for coming.
But, for some reason, I just heard a voice I didn't recognize...
でも何だか 聞き慣れない声が
混じつてたような気がするんだけど
気のせいかな ?
Is it just me?
Now that you mention it...
そういえは…
It does seem like it.
言われてみりゃ
そんな気がしねえでも…
さすがだな
I have to hand it to you.
仲間でもない
俺の声を聞き分けられるとは
To be able to isolate my voice amongst all your friends' voices...
I-It's nothing.
い いえ…
Who the heck are you anyway?
つうか お前 誰 ?
Me?
俺か? 俺は元
クレアス夕ンフイ一ルド
I used to go by Claire Stanfield, the former conductor of the Transcontinental Railway.
元 大陸横断鉄道の車掌
現 レイ丿し卜レ一サ一つてとこだ
The current Rail Tracer, you could say.
R-R-Rail Tracer?!
レ レレ レ レイ丿し卜レ一サ一?
あっ ジヤグジ一!
Jacuzzi!
急な話で申し訳ないんだがな
Forgive me for the sudden change of subject, but...
I have business I must attend to with the girl over there.
俺は そこの女に用があるんだ
ちよつと邪魔するぞ
Excuse me for a second.
It's been a while.
久しぷりだな…
まだ俺を殺す気か?
Do you still intend to kill me?
Well, it's not like I mind anyway.
まあ別に それでも構ゎないけどな
However, I think it's common sense to do a proper confession once.
だけど 一度はちゃんと
告白しておくのが筋だろうと思つてな
I don't believe my true feelings were properly conveyed on that train.
あの列車の上では 俺の想いというやつを
伝えてなかった気がする
To be straightforward...
ス卜レ一 卜に言うが…
I love you so much from the bottom of my heart it troubles me, Chane.
困つたことに俺は 心の底から
シヤ一ネを愛してるみたいだ…
My apologies. That's a lie.
悪い ウソついた
実は困らない
Actually, I'm not troubled.
でも愛してるのは本当だ
But it's true that I love you.
ああ やつぱり言葉を飾るなんてのは
性に合わないな
As I thought, it doesn't fit my nature to use fancy words.
ス卜レ一 卜に言うと…
To put it straightly...
I love you, so let's get married.
好きだ 結婚しよう
不安か?
Are you worried?
It's all right! I promise you.
大丈夫だ 約束する
俺は お前の信じてきた世界を
壊さない
I won't shatter the world you've come come to believe in.
Your world isn't that fragile.
世界は そんなにヤヮ じやない
人が入り込んで
壊れる世界なんてないさ
There is no world that would fall apart when someone else comes in.
It will only grow more, that's all.
ただ広がるだけ それだけだ
If your world seems like it's breaking down, I'll protect you.
お前の世界が壊れそうになったら
俺が守つてやる
Someone who says such things is normally not a trustworthy person.
こんな言葉を使う奴は 普通は
信用できないだろうけどな だ力ヾ…
But, as you know, I'm not normal.
知つてのとおり 俺は普通じやない
{シヤ一ネ丿
な甘だうう…
なせこの入庭ちな私の庭めノご…
I wonder why...
Why do these people go to such lengths for me?
出会フ ごまだ渇貼 なC )私 の盧めに
For someone they have only met recently...
Even though we aren't family...
家族 さも な c '私 の庭めノご
ここまさレごく力るの盧ろう?
I wonder why they're still helping me now...
Why does this man say that he loves me?
この男峡 なぜ
私き好きだと言うのだろぅ?
I've never met another person who has told me they loved me before.
私き好きだと言う入晨フ虹
鱧会っ庭ことなな汝フ庭
ノ敏渇タも私 き避ノプ潅
Even my comrades avoid me.
又ヵらも愛レご‥るなどと
言ゎ力庭こ とななヵっ庭のに
Father never told me he loved me either.
That's right...
そう 又ヵらも…
Not even my own father...
...has said...
愛レごいるなどと…
言ゎれ庭ことなな汝フ庭…
...he loved me.
あ一 理解不能な話を しよう
Let's talk about a story beyond comprehension.
理解できないということは
人間の営みにおいて どういうことだ?
What does "beyond comprehension" mean in human actions?
理解できないな
I can't comprehend it.
まあ いい そんなものは
者えるだけ無駄だ…
Whatever. There's no use in thinking about it.
というわけで よく分からないが
状況を再開してもいいのか?
So, that aside, is it all right if we continue where we last left off?
Very well. I'll permit it.
いいだろう 俺が許可しよう
さてまあ シヤ一ネに答えを
聞いていないゎけだが
Well now, I haven't received a response from you yet, but...
for the time being, if you insist on opposing Chane and her friends, I'll be your opponent.
とりあえず シヤ一ネとその伸間に
敵対するのなら 俺が相手になろう
よし 逃げるなら今のうちだぞ
All right! You should run while you still can.
What an arrogant man!
なんという尊大な奴だ !
There is only one person I know who rivals that arrogance...
俺の中で その尊大さに
匹敵する人間はー人しかいない!
That's Brother Ladd!
ラ
ノ 卜の兄貴だ !
Brother Ladd's arrogance is unshakable.
ラツ ドの兄貴の尊大さは
揺るぎないのだから
それを脅かすお前は
大変けしからん!
Therefore, you shall not be forgiven for threatening it!
If I don't put your arrogance below Brother Ladd's,
お前の尊大さを少なくとも
ラツ ドの兄貴以下にしてやらなければ
俺の夜は明けず 太陽も見ない !
dawn will not come for me!
いずれにしても夜のままだ !
Either way, it will be night all day!
ラツ ドつてのは 丿しツソファ三リ一の
ラツド丿しッソのことか?
By Ladd, do you mean Ladd Russo of the Russo family by any chance?
Y-You know Big Brother?
なつ ? 兄貢を知つているのか
こないだ列車から落ちた奴だろ ?
The guy who fell off the train the other day, right?
なぜそれを知つている ?
How did you know that?
身内以外に噂で
流れるような話じゃないぞ
It's not a rumor that would be known amongst outsiders.
That's because the one who dropped him was me.
だって 落としたの俺だし
dokomade mo tsuzuiteru hoshizora miagete utau
I sing, looking up into the endless starry night.
kagiriaru bokutachi no eien wo yume miru melody
A melody in a dream... about our limited eternity.
mune ni afureru itoshisa no mizu wa
This water of love, overflowing from my chest...
mirai no hate de dareka ni todoku darou
I wonder if it will reach someone in the future?
shinjite iruyo
I will believe in you.
harukana toki wo kake nukete
Transcending generations of time...
bokutachi no yobigoe wa itsuka ookina uta ni naru
Will our calls turn into a beautiful song one day?
ai wo tsumuide yukeru yo
You can start building your love,
ima wa mada konnani chiisana hikari dakedo
Though right now, the light is still faint.
Next ep
Preview
Carol Realizes That the Story
Cannot Have an Ending
They say human will is limited.
However, there are people who say that when finding unlimited possibilities,
humans are able to amplify their lives 10 times, 100 times, and even 1000 times.
That's quite understandable, but in the center of that should be me!
That's the rule, isn't it?